<resources>
<!--    <array name="emo_images">-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/happy</item>-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/sad</item>-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/angry</item>-->
<!--    </array>-->

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="app_name">EmoGuess</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_play">PlayActivity</string>
    <string name="error_camera_permission_denied" />
    <string name="error_cannot_open" />
    <string name="error_cannot_write" />
    <string name="error_cannot_get_permission" />
    <string name="error_not_having_camera" />


    <string name="btn_tittle_capture_image" />
    <string name="how_to_play_parents">\u2022 For both, images and videos, guess the emotion based on how the child enacts it per emotion card. \n \u2022 Hold the phone in landscape mode, such that the screen faces the child and is not visible to you. \n \u2022 For every correct guess, use your left finger to tap the left side of the screen, and for every incorrect guess, use your right finger to tap the right side of the screen. \n \u2022 Capture the child\'s expression for every emotion card using the \'volume down\' button. \n \u2022 Make sure the phone is stable while clicking the picture. \n \u2022 Ensure the volume is set appropriately before you enter into the game session. \n \u2022 During the game, the volume can be adjusted only using \'volume up\' button, as \'volume down\' will be used as a camera button. \n \u2022 Keep going till the timer stops, and get your score in the end.</string>
    <string name="how_to_share_parents">\u2022 The expressions you capture during the game get saved to your gallery automatically. \n \u2022 After the game ends, you will see a share button on the next screen, clicking which will take you to the gallery, from where you select the images to be shared. \n \u2022 In case you forget to do this after the game ends, there is also an option in the play area which you may use for the same.</string>
    <string name="how_to_children">How to Play: Carefully look at the image/video on the screen (with text below it as the hint). Enact the emotion shown by the image/video. Tell your parents if they guessed it right :)</string>
    <string name="hyperlink">Contact us at <a href="https://hmi.iiitd.edu.in/contact_us.html">HMI Lab</a></string>
    <string name="for_parents">For Parents</string>

    <string-array name="emotions">
        <item>happy</item>
        <item>sad</item>
        <item>angry</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    <array name="emo_videos">-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/happy</item>-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/sad</item>-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/angry</item>-->
    <!--    </array>-->

</resources>


