<resources>
<!--    <array name="emo_images">-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/happy</item>-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/sad</item>-->
<!--        <item>@drawable/angry</item>-->
<!--    </array>-->

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="app_name">EmoGuess</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_play">PlayActivity</string>
    <string name="error_camera_permission_denied" />
    <string name="error_cannot_open" />
    <string name="error_cannot_write" />
    <string name="error_cannot_get_permission" />
    <string name="error_not_having_camera" />


    <string name="btn_tittle_capture_image" />
    <string name="how_to_play_parents">Hold the phone according to the landscape mode, such that the screen faces the child and is not visible to you. For both, images and videos, flip to get the next one, and for every card, guess the emotion based on how the child enacts it, as well as capture their expressions using the \'volume down\' button (meanwhile, the volume can be adjusted using \'volume up\' button). For every correct guess, flip forward, and for every incorrect guess, flip backward, and get your score in the end. Keep going till the timer stops.</string>
    <string name="how_to_share_parents">The expressions you capture during the game get saved to your gallery automatically. After the game ends, you will see a share button on the next screen, clicking which will take you to the gallery, from where you select the images to be shared. In case you forget to do this after the game ends, there is also an option in the play area which you may use for the same.</string>
    <string name="how_to_children">How to Play: Carefully look at the image/video on the screen (with text below it as the hint). Enact the emotion shown by the image/video. Tell your parents if they guessed it right :)</string>
    <string name="for_parents">For Parents</string>

    <string-array name="emotions">
        <item>happy</item>
        <item>sad</item>
        <item>angry</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    <array name="emo_videos">-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/happy</item>-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/sad</item>-->
    <!--        <item>@drawable/angry</item>-->
    <!--    </array>-->

</resources>


